Mama?
Well, your dad always picks you up, right?
Daikichi isn't my dad.
My dad is Grandpa.
That's weird!
Everyone has a mom and dad.
So, what's Daikichi?
I don't know...
What's that supposed to mean?!
You're so weird, Rin!
Men can't have babies!
Shut up!
You don't need a dad!
Dummies!
It takes one to know one.
Dummy, dummy, dummy!
Ms. Hiro!
Let's go!
Kouki called me a dummy!
Kouki kept saying dummy!
Ms. Hiro!
Kouki, do you only live with your mom?
My dad went off somewhere, and then they got a divorce.
What's a "divorce"?
It's like quitting marriage!
Maybe my mom is gone because she got a divorce...
Who knows?
If you don't wear your hat, they'll get mad at you.
What?
Look, your string is stretched out.
Rin! Your dad's here!
Rin!
It's Daikichi!
He's here to pick you up!
Wiin, pibbup!
Maa, are you okay?
Thank you.
See you tomorrow, Rin.
Goodbye!
What do you feel like having for dinner?
Um, let's see...
Kouki!
Your mom's here to pick you up!
Bunny Drop
I dunno about tomorrow.
It's different than a sacrifice. Something's off.
I don't think it's like some penalty game.
So, why? I don't get it at all.
I'm a little bit unsatisfied, but your presence
right now is more than just important.
There's no such thing in this world
as something never-ending.
Crying isn't painful, it's love's sweet drops, sweet drops!
I want to keep dreaming forever, ya know?
I want to be more kind, ya know?
As long as I'm with you, I'm happy.
Girls sure are strong, ya know?
But sometimes we're weak, ya know?
Our wish is to be happy, happy, happy!
And those days will be happy, too!
Just wanna make you happy!
Your mom's beautiful, isn't she?
More like a noisy old bat!
U-Um...
Apparently, Rin always looks after Kouki...
R-Really?
My son can be a little abrasive, so he's had trouble making friends...
Thank you so much.
Oh no! Not at all...
I-I should be thanking you...
My Rin is incredibly unsociable...
Maybe it's like birds of a feather flock together, huh?
Daikichi! You were just talking about me, weren't you?!
I wasn't saying anything bad.
Now, walk faster.
Don't beg me to carry you home again.
I won't beg!
Let's go!
Is Rin a "Daddy's girl"?
Oh, I'm not her father.
I'm more like a relative, or...
I-I'm sorry, what was I thinking?!
Oh, don't worry about it!
Mom, you're too slow!
It's nice that you made a friend, huh?
Yep!
Kouki said that he doesn't have a dad.
He said his dad went somewhere after the divorce.
Rin... Do you know what divorce is?
Yeah. When marriage is finished, right?
Yeah, more or less...
If God finds out, He punishes them, doesn't He?
Mmm...
I wonder if my mom is gone because of divorce too...
Do you want to meet her?
Dunno.
I see.
But you know...
If she's like Kouki's mom, I think I would like her!
Me too! Definitely!
What?!
Rin's mother is...
Yeah. Grandpa's maid is probably Rin's mother.
I don't believe it...
Have you heard anything about the maid?
This was pretty cool.
A farewell party? For me?
I'm sorry it took so long to set up.
Winter sales have finally settled down, so...
Thanks.
I can't really go out at night, though.
I have a six year old at home.
Are you telling me you haven't even gone out once?
Yeah. I just can't.
I don't even think about going drinking anymore.
Maybe I'm just getting old...
You're only thirty.
Well, the people in my shipping department are young,
but a lot of them have kids.
We don't normally go drinking anyway.
Right?
You got that right.
I gotta pick up the kid from kindergarten.
We had two kids in two years and the youngest is 3 months old,
so if I don't get home quick, my wife...
Turns into "Wifezilla", right?
Monsters are nothing compared to when she's mad.
Kawachi!
Hey, Gotou!
I heard about the farewell party!
Yeah, but I can't go out at night, so...
They went to the trouble of arranging it,
so why don't you bring the kid along?
I'll bring mine, too!
You want to go drinking once in a while too, huh?
No worries, it'll be fine!
I'll be looking forward to it!
All right, I'm coming...
Daikichi, the phone.
Thanks.
Hello?
Daikichi? It seems Grandpa had a maid from some agency...
Whoa, whoa, wait a second...
Do you have her name?
Yoshii Masako, spelled with the characters for "correct" and "child".
That's the name on the maternal health record, isn't it?
I believe so...
Are you going to contact her?
She abandoned that precious child...
Calm down.
You saw the health record, right?
There's a lot written in there...
There's so much that we still don't know.
Excuse me!
What I'm saying is...
I don't know the difference between work and home anymore!
Sorry I'm late.
Hey, slacker! C'mere!
Get away from me, you drunk!
Rin? You came!
It's nice to see you!
You're so adorable!
Eat all you want!
Here you go.
I'm glad you're here, Rin.
Thank you!
Here you are, Rin.
Is orange juice okay?
Mm-hm!
Rin's beautiful, isn't she?
Yep, she sure is!
You're embarrassing her!
Yuu, let me help you.
Thank you, Rin!
Kawachi, don't hold back!
Rin might sleep on the way home, so...
Rin, I'm going to the washroom.
"Bathroom"!
Yeah, yeah, "bathroom".
He left our section high and dry.
You shouldn't produce results, and then bail!
Quitting while you're ahead is dirty!
Sales have been tough this month...
Even if we do a decent job selling,
management won't look at anything but last year's results!
What are we gonna do?
This sucks...
The old me would've stormed in and ripped them a new one, but...
I really need to pee.
Girls are so soft!
I wanna take you home!
What's important to me has changed.
Kawachi.
About your transfer...
After seeing Rin, I've come around.
Yeah?
Mama! Mama!
I wanna hold her forever!
Pick me up, too!
Gotou, Rin doesn't wanna be held!
Masako...
What were you thinking when you left her behind?
Yuu was really cute, wasn't he?
You sure do love little kids.
Yep! The mail came.
Thanks.
An elementary school admission information session, huh?
I don't even have to do any research this time.
What's wrong?
Is there an admissions test?
No, no, no!
You can get in without taking a test!
Really?
Yeah, for sure!
Compulsory education is just that awesome!
You're so drunk!
Shoot! How's this?!
Rin, he's here!
S-sorry for being late.
Everyone else already left!
My bad...
Kouki, your mother's here too!
Sorry, Kouki...
H-Hello.
It's been... a while.
Daikichi, are we gonna make it in time?
I'll grab a taxi!
Sorry!
Name tags can be turned around,
and they must be turned on the way home from school, so that their names aren't visible.
You must also tell your child not to be alone at a park.
And don't forget to tell them not to follow strangers.
It's tough, isn't it?
Instead of teaching them to trust people,
we have to teach them to be suspicious.
Yeah...
That one sheet we were given...
Whoops.
I'll carry them! I've got them!
How do you know what vaccinations they've had?
S-Sorry.
Looks like I should know this...
Not at all...
Do you have Rin's health record?
Yeah, at home...
Maternal Health Record
It has a vaccination record page.
Now you know!
I see...
I really don't know anything.
See, I just met Rin about three months ago...
Three months?
Yeah...
That's a surprise.
I mean, Rin looks like she really trusts you, Daikichi.
I'm not sure about that...
At home, she's really sassy and noisy.
That's proof she trusts you.
It's obvious that she sees you as family.
Family...
R-Really?
Sure!
Maybe...
What?
I just jumped over your shadow!
I'm not tired!
That's okay.
Put me down!
Put me down right now!
Thanks.
She has almost everything on the list.
Bookbag?
Not yet...
Well, you'd better!
All the designer label and cute ones are sold out by now!
A normal one is fine.
She's a girl, so "normal" won't work!
Fine, I'll look this weekend.
Dai, are you going to really raise Rin?
After all, you transferred to another section, right?
I haven't really thought ahead that far...
Mama!
Now I'll do your hair!
Okay!
You two are close, huh?
Mothers and daughters are like friends.
Come to think of it, Mom and Kazumi are like buddies too...
Who's to say that Masako's situation hasn't changed
and she wants Rin back?
Look at how many shots she's had...
Her mother must have...
Souichi's Will
Boing!
A will!
"Boing"?
"If Masako found it, she would probably get rid of it.
Thus, I've taken this... roundabout method.
However, I don't really know the proper way to write a secret... riddle?
And this "keyboard" thing is making a fool out of me,
so I can't proceed at but a snail's pace."
Come on, these character conversion mistakes are dreadful!
"Already, this feeble-minded old fool's energy is exhausted.
Therefore, I'm giving up on this blog..."
That's too soon!
What happened to the "greatest generation"?!
"To be continued in Rin's maternal health record..."
Sorry, Rin...
Let me have a look-see here...
Since I'm guessing that the person who will find this piece of paper loves Rin,
I shall give an account here of Rin and her mother, Masako.
Masako is easily misunderstood,
so I would like to start by saying that she is by no means a bad girl.
She knows that she's a failure of a mother.
She feels sorry for Rin.
Even now, she persists on being my maid.
I believe that she will continue to do so.
I think of that as Rin's greatest happiness.
Happy? What does he mean?
She's living a vigilant life, carefully leaving no traces of herself behind,
so that if something should happen to me,
her existence will be hidden from all of my relatives.
Masako certainly has a mother's love for Rin.
But she's still young and may not yet have the maturity to be a parent...
I don't really understand it...
But the one thing that's clear is that he cared about Rin and her mother.
Yoshii Masako
Daikichi!
W-What?!
Listen!
I want you to make my hair look like rabbit ears!
What?
Like what Reina's mom did before!
I can't!
Do it!
There's no way I can do it! It's outta my league!
You will do it!
'Cause...
she said I wasn't cute!
Huh?
Someone said that?
Mii said I wasn't cute at all!
Really?
I think you win, hands down.
I wanna be cute, too...
All right, all right...
She's already grown to be a fine girl
and that means her feelings can definitely be hurt...
Masako, did you know...?
Rin's mind has already developed a lot.
She's mature in a lot of ways.
That's why she needs an adult to keep an eye on her.
Fin...ished!
This is...
Twinkle, twinkle, little star...
H-Hey, Rin...
How I wonder what you...
What are you doing?
It's a secret, so I can't tell anyone at home about Parents' Day!
What? Parents' Day?
You can't look!
S-She's gonna do it with that hairstyle?
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
Yoshii Masako
How I wonder what you are.
If you left Rin alone,
thinking she'd eventually forget something as painful as that...
Up above the world so high,
Like a diamond in the sky.
I have no problems with hating you.
Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
You better at least have a damn good reason.
But...
How I wonder what you are.
what could possibly be a good reason for abandoning a child?
Study desk
Study chair
This one's cute!
Well yeah, it's cute.
But you're going to be using it for a long time, so we want something a little more...
Oh, I know!
A desk that looks like it's for a young lady would be better, don't you think?
Young lady?
Yeah! One that's for a young lady is good!
Yeah!
You're sitting there again?
Do I look like a young lady?
Yeah. And I think you can still use the desk
when you're a high school student.
Is a high school student an adult?
I guess that's half an adult...
Listen to me read!
"A girl went alone into a forest to play.
She lost her way and looked for the path to get back home,
but she just couldn't find it.
Suddenly, before she knew it, there was a tiny house in the forest."
Is this Yoshii?
Yes...
A sunny early Sunday afternoon
Let's go somewhere today
It's the same road I'm used to traveling
But I can see it sparkling so bright
With the sun shining down its warmth
And you here by my side...
I'm already high, high, high
I feel like dashing out
Sing, la, la, la
My voice out to forever
I'm already high, high, high
Ride the dancing wind
Sing, la, la, la
My voice springs up
This is cute, isn't it?
Again?! Rin!
Rin!
Hey!
Daikichi...
I told you not to run off on your own like that!
Okay...
What's that?
It can make me into a young lady!
No way!
This is for much later!
Why?